gokira.ca 2014-06-10

# Privacy Policy- Gokira Free Classified Read Privacy Policy / Buy and Sell online for Free

This privacy policy describes how the Gokira.ca website, tools, applications, and services (*Gokira.ca*) handle your personal information. Gokira.ca collects, uses, and shares personal information to help Gokira.ca work and to keep Gokira.ca safe (details below).  This policy is effective June 13, 2012.

**Collection.**  Information posted on Gokira.ca is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in the United States and elsewhere in the world where Gokira.ca has facilities. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to Gokira.ca's collection, use, disclosure of your personal information and to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers in the United States and elsewhere in the world where Gokira.ca has facilities. Gokira.ca collects and stores the following personal information:

  * email address, phone numbers, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information (including credit card and billing information);
  * computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Gokira.ca and ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site);
  * other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

**Use.**  Gokira.ca uses users' personal information to:

  * provide our services;
  * track, confirm and fulfill purchases;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;
  * customize, measure, and improve user experience and our services, content, and advertising;
  * deliver targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers to you according to your preferences;
  * do other things for users as described when Gokira.ca collects the information.

**Disclosure.**  Gokira.ca doesn't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. Gokira.ca may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Gokira.ca may also share personal information with:

  * corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).
  * service providers who help with our business operations.
  * third-party websites and publishers so ads (or the content of the ads) published on Gokira.ca can also be published on a broader array of venues or information vehicles.

**Communications and email tools.  **You agree to receive marketing communications from us unless you tell us that you prefer not to receive such communications. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply indicate your preference by following directions provided with the communication. You may not use our site or communication tools to harvest addresses, send spam or otherwise breach our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. Gokira.ca may automatically scan and manually filter messages sent via our communication tools for malicious activity or prohibited content, but Gokira.ca does not permanently store such messages. Gokira.ca Canada reserves the right to delay replies in cases of suspected fraudulent activity or violations of the [Gokira.ca Terms of Use](http://help.kijiji.net/ca/knowledgebase.php?article=92) and/or to refuse to transmit messages. If you use our tools to send content to a friend, Gokira.ca doesn't permanently store your friends' addresses or use or disclose them for marketing purposes. To report spam from other users, please contact customer support. 

**Access, Modification, and Deletion.**  You can see, modify or erase most of your personal information by reviewing and modifying your posting or account status page, by signing on to My Gokira.ca or by contacting customer support to review any personal information Gokira.ca stores that is not available on Gokira.ca. There may a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. Gokira.ca deletes personal information when Gokira.ca no longer needs it for the purposes we described earlier. Gokira.ca retains personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back. If you have further questions you can contact customer support. 

**Transfer of Personal Data to Other Cot Export Private Limited Companies.**  We may share your information with members of the Cot Export Private Limited corporate family - like batteryfordiscount.com to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you've requested their services. 

**Security.**  Gokira.ca uses lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but as you probably know, nothing's perfect, so Gokira.ca makes no guarantees.

**Cookies.**  Gokira.ca or our service providers may use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * Gokira.ca offers certain features that are available only through the use of cookies.
  * Gokira.ca uses cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services. For more information on your choices about accepting cookies, consult your browser help function.

Gokira.ca sometimes works with service providers who may place cookies on your computer to serve and measure the effectiveness of ads on our or our advertising partners' behalf and collect anonymous information about how you use websites owned by Gokira.ca and its affiliates. This information allows them to help us customize our content and advertising. Gokira.ca does not allow these companies to collect any personal information about you using these cookies. For more information about why Gokira.ca uses cookies, see Cookie, Web Beacons, and Your Privacy. 

**General.**  Gokira.ca may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next use the site or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If Gokira.ca or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, Gokira.ca may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to [customer support](http://help.kijiji.net/ca/index.php?a=add).
